[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "IN", "DT", ",", "VB", "POS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 44, "question": "What is your take on what has gone down today with him and his girlfriend?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "take", "on", "what", "has", "gone", "down", "today", "with", "him", "and", "his", "girlfriend", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RP", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 45, "answer": "Well first of all, let's look at the context.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "first", "of", "all", ",", "let", "'s", "look", "at", "the", "context", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "CC", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 110, "question": "Why is that I feel myself warming to him?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "is", "that", "I", "feel", "myself", "warming", "to", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 111, "answer": "Because you can imagine sitting down and having a beer with him and he's not going to judge you, and he loves football.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "you", "can", "imagine", "sitting", "down", "and", "having", "a", "beer", "with", "him", "and", "he", "'s", "not", "going", "to", "judge", "you", ",", "and", "he", "loves", "football", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJS", "NNS", "VBZ", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 114, "question": "But if that was a criteria for being a politician, I mean almost all of them would have to give up their jobs, wouldn't they?", "question_tokens": ["But", "if", "that", "was", "a", "criteria", "for", "being", "a", "politician", ",", "I", "mean", "almost", "all", "of", "them", "would", "have", "to", "give", "up", "their", "jobs", ",", "would", "n't", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "DT", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 115, "answer": "Well, I don't think personal feeling for most politicians is smoking crack.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "personal", "feeling", "for", "most", "politicians", "is", "smoking", "crack", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 156, "question": "You ever got drunk before, Bill?", "question_tokens": ["You", "ever", "got", "drunk", "before", ",", "Bill", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "NN", "IN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 157, "answer": "Of course.", "answer_tokens": ["Of", "course", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 165, "question": "What changed your mind?", "question_tokens": ["What", "changed", "your", "mind", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 166, "answer": "Well, I was part of the agenda.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "was", "part", "of", "the", "agenda", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 235, "question": "Can he stumble on as a figure head or is this the beginning of the end do you feel?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "he", "stumble", "on", "as", "a", "figure", "head", "or", "is", "this", "the", "beginning", "of", "the", "end", "do", "you", "feel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "VBZ", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 236, "answer": "Well, he retains some statutory powers that are conferred to him by the province.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "he", "retains", "some", "statutory", "powers", "that", "are", "conferred", "to", "him", "by", "the", "province", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 270, "question": "Do you feel now vindicated by events, so in a sense it's probably much more plausible what you claim for given his way he's been admitting stuff?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "now", "vindicated", "by", "events", ",", "so", "in", "a", "sense", "it", "'s", "probably", "much", "more", "plausible", "what", "you", "claim", "for", "given", "his", "way", "he", "'s", "been", "admitting", "stuff", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "RBR", "JJ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 271, "answer": "Vindicated is such an empty feeling.", "answer_tokens": ["Vindicated", "is", "such", "an", "empty", "feeling", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 277, "question": "Is he hurting Toronto?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "he", "hurting", "Toronto", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 278, "answer": "I think he is.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "he", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Toronto"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 283, "question": "If that guy is the mayor, what's the rest of them like?", "question_tokens": ["If", "that", "guy", "is", "the", "mayor", ",", "what", "'s", "the", "rest", "of", "them", "like", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 284, "answer": "Well, the businesses aren't saying it's not.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "businesses", "are", "n't", "saying", "it", "'s", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 286, "question": "Is he damaging Toronto?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "he", "damaging", "Toronto", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 287, "answer": "I think it is.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Toronto"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 299, "question": "Was he just being rambunctious Rob Ford or was he being a very unpleasant harasser in your view?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "he", "just", "being", "rambunctious", "Rob", "Ford", "or", "was", "he", "being", "a", "very", "unpleasant", "harasser", "in", "your", "view", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 300, "answer": "He was completely stoned.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "was", "completely", "stoned", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rob Ford"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 306, "question": "Did he see toes?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "he", "see", "toes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 307, "answer": "No comment.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "comment", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Toronto", "Toronto"]}, "docId": "131118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 313, "question": "What do you say to that charge?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "say", "to", "that", "charge", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 314, "answer": "I think it's all about Toronto and I think we have to start thinking about Toronto.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "all", "about", "Toronto", "and", "I", "think", "we", "have", "to", "start", "thinking", "about", "Toronto", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Toronto"]}, "docId": "131118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 323, "question": "A lot of other people are thinking, \"Wow, this is all quite fun,\" isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["A", "lot", "of", "other", "people", "are", "thinking", ",", "``", "Wow", ",", "this", "is", "all", "quite", "fun", ",", "''", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "``", "NNP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "VBN", ",", "''", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 324, "answer": "I don't think a lot of the media is saying he's damaging Toronto.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "a", "lot", "of", "the", "media", "is", "saying", "he", "'s", "damaging", "Toronto", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 329, "question": "Has he been a quite effective mayor as he claims?", "question_tokens": ["Has", "he", "been", "a", "quite", "effective", "mayor", "as", "he", "claims", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 330, "answer": "I think he's exceptionally good at setting a conservative tone.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "he", "'s", "exceptionally", "good", "at", "setting", "a", "conservative", "tone", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["billion dollars", "$200 million"]}, "docId": "131118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NNS", ",", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "RP", "$", "CD", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 335, "question": "So, do you think -- but Sarah he's been achieving that and keeping a good, tight fist on the expenditure, who cares if he gets drunk occasionally?", "question_tokens": ["So", ",", "do", "you", "think", "--", "but", "Sarah", "he", "'s", "been", "achieving", "that", "and", "keeping", "a", "good", ",", "tight", "fist", "on", "the", "expenditure", ",", "who", "cares", "if", "he", "gets", "drunk", "occasionally", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ":", "CC", "NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "CC", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 336, "answer": "He's been claiming that he saved a billion dollars, city government costs of rate has gone up $200 million.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "'s", "been", "claiming", "that", "he", "saved", "a", "billion", "dollars", ",", "city", "government", "costs", "of", "rate", "has", "gone", "up", "$", "200", "million", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sarah"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 345, "question": "Is he that naughty?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "he", "that", "naughty", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 346, "answer": "He's quite naughty.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "'s", "quite", "naughty", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 360, "question": "He can survive this?", "question_tokens": ["He", "can", "survive", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 361, "answer": "Yeah, he'll cling.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "he", "'ll", "cling", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 375, "question": "How are you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 376, "answer": "Terrific.", "answer_tokens": ["Terrific", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 412, "question": "How brutal is a Presidential campaign?", "question_tokens": ["How", "brutal", "is", "a", "Presidential", "campaign", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 413, "answer": "It's brutal.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "brutal", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJS", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 421, "question": "And what was the worst moment?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "was", "the", "worst", "moment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 422, "answer": "The best moment is seeing the people.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "best", "moment", "is", "seeing", "the", "people", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 435, "question": "Outside of the moment you lost obviously, what was the lowest moment of the whole thing?", "question_tokens": ["Outside", "of", "the", "moment", "you", "lost", "obviously", ",", "what", "was", "the", "lowest", "moment", "of", "the", "whole", "thing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 436, "answer": "Well, you know, the election night I have to say it was pretty darn low.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "the", "election", "night", "I", "have", "to", "say", "it", "was", "pretty", "darn", "low", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 438, "question": "Did you go into that night and genuinely thinking you could still pull it off?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "go", "into", "that", "night", "and", "genuinely", "thinking", "you", "could", "still", "pull", "it", "off", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 439, "answer": "I was getting nervous on election day.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "getting", "nervous", "on", "election", "day", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 458, "question": "And in particular the President's position that he's found himself in?", "question_tokens": ["And", "in", "particular", "the", "President", "'s", "position", "that", "he", "'s", "found", "himself", "in", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 459, "answer": "Well, you know, he's put himself in a very sticky place because you either have to think that he was not telling the truth or he's grossly incompetent.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "he", "'s", "put", "himself", "in", "a", "very", "sticky", "place", "because", "you", "either", "have", "to", "think", "that", "he", "was", "not", "telling", "the", "truth", "or", "he", "'s", "grossly", "incompetent", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 461, "question": "Which side are you leaning towards?", "question_tokens": ["Which", "side", "are", "you", "leaning", "towards", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 462, "answer": "I think a little bit of both.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "a", "little", "bit", "of", "both", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 463, "question": "You think he lied?", "question_tokens": ["You", "think", "he", "lied", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 464, "answer": "I don't think he was telling the truth.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "he", "was", "telling", "the", "truth", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 465, "question": "It's the same thing, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "the", "same", "thing", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 466, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 473, "question": "What's it called?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "it", "called", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 474, "answer": "A fluffernutter.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "fluffernutter", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 502, "question": "Is he is the type of candidate?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "he", "is", "the", "type", "of", "candidate", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 503, "answer": "If he absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["If", "he", "absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 506, "question": "You wouldn't be having many of these if runs, will he?", "question_tokens": ["You", "would", "n't", "be", "having", "many", "of", "these", "if", "runs", ",", "will", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "IN", "NNS", ",", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 507, "answer": "I hope not.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "hope", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 508, "question": "The -- what are they called again?", "question_tokens": ["The", "--", "what", "are", "they", "called", "again", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", ":", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 509, "answer": "Fluffernutters.", "answer_tokens": ["Fluffernutters", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 517, "question": "ORGAN: This has your -- one of your grandchildren?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "This", "has", "your", "--", "one", "of", "your", "grandchildren", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "DT", "VBZ", "PRP$", ":", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 518, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "PRP", "CC", ":"], "qSentId": 521, "question": "Oh, you're son?", "question_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "you", "'re", "son", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 522, "answer": "That's me and ...", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "me", "and", "..."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "CC", "RB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 533, "question": "Well, you know, wouldn't it be nice if we could always stay as young as, you know, we were in our 20s?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "would", "n't", "it", "be", "nice", "if", "we", "could", "always", "stay", "as", "young", "as", ",", "you", "know", ",", "we", "were", "in", "our", "20s", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 534, "answer": "There's also lovely pictures in here of you, your kids, your grandkids, and so on.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "'s", "also", "lovely", "pictures", "in", "here", "of", "you", ",", "your", "kids", ",", "your", "grandkids", ",", "and", "so", "on", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJR", "NNS", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 546, "question": "Would you like to see a woman president regardless of which party?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "like", "to", "see", "a", "woman", "president", "regardless", "of", "which", "party", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "WDT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 547, "answer": "You know, I'd love to see a lot of more women involved in politics.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "'d", "love", "to", "see", "a", "lot", "of", "more", "women", "involved", "in", "politics", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 552, "question": "Have you ever attempted to run?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "ever", "attempted", "to", "run", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 553, "answer": "Never.", "answer_tokens": ["Never", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 554, "question": "For any high office?", "question_tokens": ["For", "any", "high", "office", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 555, "answer": "Never.", "answer_tokens": ["Never", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 556, "question": "ORGAN: Really?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 557, "answer": "Never.", "answer_tokens": ["Never", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Annie Evans"]}, "docId": "131118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NNP", ":", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 570, "question": "It's a recipe from your Welsh grandmother, Annie Evans?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "a", "recipe", "from", "your", "Welsh", "grandmother", ",", "Annie", "Evans", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNP", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 571, "answer": "My Welsh -- Annie Evans.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "Welsh", "--", "Annie", "Evans", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Annie Evans"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kieran Matthew"]}, "docId": "131118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 582, "question": "Now, you have a new addition to the family, Kieran James Romney?", "question_tokens": ["Now", ",", "you", "have", "a", "new", "addition", "to", "the", "family", ",", "Kieran", "James", "Romney", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 583, "answer": "Kieran Matthew.", "answer_tokens": ["Kieran", "Matthew", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kieran James Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 589, "question": "And he's -- how old is he?", "question_tokens": ["And", "he", "'s", "--", "how", "old", "is", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 590, "answer": "He is about 6 months old now because we didn't legally adopt him.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "is", "about", "6", "months", "old", "now", "because", "we", "did", "n't", "legally", "adopt", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", ":"], "qSentId": 597, "question": "Anything?", "question_tokens": ["Anything", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "aSentId": 598, "answer": "You know, I'd advised him that this is not a good time in their lives that they need to ...", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "'d", "advised", "him", "that", "this", "is", "not", "a", "good", "time", "in", "their", "lives", "that", "they", "need", "to", "..."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "DT", "IN", "DT", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 604, "question": "You can do it?", "question_tokens": ["You", "can", "do", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 605, "answer": "... some of these even I could do, yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["...", "some", "of", "these", "even", "I", "could", "do", ",", "yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 628, "question": "What happened to Refalca?", "question_tokens": ["What", "happened", "to", "Refalca", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "TO", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 629, "answer": "Refalca did well.", "answer_tokens": ["Refalca", "did", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "RB", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "VBZ", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VBG", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 637, "question": "Where is Refalca?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "is", "Refalca", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 638, "answer": "She's -- I'm riding on her occasionally myself now but, you know, horses has been part of my therapy for me to getting stronger.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "'s", "--", "I", "'m", "riding", "on", "her", "occasionally", "myself", "now", "but", ",", "you", "know", ",", "horses", "has", "been", "part", "of", "my", "therapy", "for", "me", "to", "getting", "stronger", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Warren Buffett"]}, "docId": "131118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "RB", "VBZ", ",", "DT", "CD", "IN", "CD", "NN", "CC", "RB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "RB", "JJ", "RB", ":", "RB", ":", "RB", "JJ", "CC", ":", "IN", "POS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 669, "question": "In other words you can never do a good deal with a bad guy, and that with many people, a handshake is good enough for him?", "question_tokens": ["In", "other", "words", "you", "can", "never", "do", "a", "good", "deal", "with", "a", "bad", "guy", ",", "and", "that", "with", "many", "people", ",", "a", "handshake", "is", "good", "enough", "for", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 670, "answer": "Warren Buffett really is, the one on one business and just a stakeholder to the point that not make things too difficult very -- very -- very straightforward and -- that's why I like him, and I just click very well with him.", "answer_tokens": ["Warren", "Buffett", "really", "is", ",", "the", "one", "on", "one", "business", "and", "just", "a", "stakeholder", "to", "the", "point", "that", "not", "make", "things", "too", "difficult", "very", "--", "very", "--", "very", "straightforward", "and", "--", "that", "'s", "why", "I", "like", "him", ",", "and", "I", "just", "click", "very", "well", "with", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["US"]}, "docId": "131118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 679, "question": "Do you still feel confident in the way the American economy is going or do you share concerns that many people have that it's--it could potentially if they're not careful rebound back into some kind of recession?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "still", "feel", "confident", "in", "the", "way", "the", "American", "economy", "is", "going", "or", "do", "you", "share", "concerns", "that", "many", "people", "have", "that", "it", "'s", "--", "it", "could", "potentially", "if", "they", "'re", "not", "careful", "rebound", "back", "into", "some", "kind", "of", "recession", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "WDT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 680, "answer": "I have a lot of respect and have a lot of confidence for the US economy, no doubt about that.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "a", "lot", "of", "respect", "and", "have", "a", "lot", "of", "confidence", "for", "the", "US", "economy", ",", "no", "doubt", "about", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 693, "question": "Why did you like Twitter so much?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "did", "you", "like", "Twitter", "so", "much", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 694, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 715, "question": "And what does he mean by that?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "does", "he", "mean", "by", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 716, "answer": "I think he means, you know, you're quite often get seen with very large palaces and yachts and all that kinds of things.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "he", "means", ",", "you", "know", ",", "you", "'re", "quite", "often", "get", "seen", "with", "very", "large", "palaces", "and", "yachts", "and", "all", "that", "kinds", "of", "things", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Netanyahu"], "LOCATION": ["Israel"]}, "docId": "131118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 732, "question": "One of the great players in the Middle East, what do you make of what's going on here, with this tension now between -- clear tension between Netanyahu and what he believes is going on with Iran and the America and everybody else?", "question_tokens": ["One", "of", "the", "great", "players", "in", "the", "Middle", "East", ",", "what", "do", "you", "make", "of", "what", "'s", "going", "on", "here", ",", "with", "this", "tension", "now", "between", "--", "clear", "tension", "between", "Netanyahu", "and", "what", "he", "believes", "is", "going", "on", "with", "Iran", "and", "the", "America", "and", "everybody", "else", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "IN", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", ":", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 733, "answer": "Yeah, as Mr. Netanyahu said that you really find the majority of the Arab World in complete sync and alliance with the concepts of Israel.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "as", "Mr.", "Netanyahu", "said", "that", "you", "really", "find", "the", "majority", "of", "the", "Arab", "World", "in", "complete", "sync", "and", "alliance", "with", "the", "concepts", "of", "Israel", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Netanyahu"], "LOCATION": ["Middle East", "Iran", "America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 737, "question": "Do you trust Assad when he says he'll give up his chemical weapons?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "trust", "Assad", "when", "he", "says", "he", "'ll", "give", "up", "his", "chemical", "weapons", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RP", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 738, "answer": "IN TALAL: It's not that it's trust.", "answer_tokens": ["IN", "TALAL", ":", "It", "'s", "not", "that", "it", "'s", "trust", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 748, "question": "Giving people back in Saudi Arabia fully understand the dangers of what is going on here?", "question_tokens": ["Giving", "people", "back", "in", "Saudi", "Arabia", "fully", "understand", "the", "dangers", "of", "what", "is", "going", "on", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 749, "answer": "That's a very good question.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "a", "very", "good", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Saudi Arabia"]}}]